Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/kelsey-di-lulloms-48043852 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Analysis Project Management Strategy

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual) Spanish (Limited Working)

Publications

The Pressure Regime of the Northern Gulf of Mexico - Geostatistical Estimation and Regional Controls

Kelsey Di Lullo, MS

Data Scientist at Glidewell Laboratories

Orange County, California Area

Summary

Data scientist with an entrepreneurial spirit and skillset spanning predictive analytics, scientific research, software development, business operations, and marketing. Current focus is on the acquisition, analysis, and predictive applications of unstructured (text) data.

Passionate about science, technology, and the 'greater good'.

Experience

Glidewell Dental 5 years 10 months

Data Scientist

December 2016 - Present (3 years 4 months)

Newport Beach, CA

Utilize statistical, programmatic, research and analysis skills to assist with data-driven decision making throughout the company.

Data Analyst

June 2014 - Present (5 years 10 months)

Newport Beach, CA

Design & conduct analyses that support strategic initiatives. Report to CIO and provide competitive analyses on various research projects and analytic/programming projects.

Northwestern University School of Professional Studies Graduate Teaching Assistant

December 2017 - Present (2 years 4 months)

Assist with Web Analytics course, focusing on web scraping, social media & network analysis.

Also assisted with Practical Machine Learning Course using Python.

TechShift Co-Founder February 2015 - December 2017 (2 years 11 months) Tustin, CA

TechShift is a California 501c(3) nonprofit that provides educational web and data science applications for underserved communities.

Earth Science Associates
Research Associate
August 2012 - April 2014 (1 year 9 months)
Long Beach

Performed geotechnical research and analysis for small GIS software company based in Long Beach.

Education

Northwestern University

Master's Degree, Predictive Analytics (Data Science) · (2014 - 2016)

Florida State University
Bachelor's Degree, Geography · (2006 - 2010)